[{"answer": "Well, what I can see, Piers, is that the eastern part of the country seems to be under the control of anti-Gadhafi forces.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What do you know?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "And we could see a completely different situation to the one we saw in Egypt, couldn't we?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "What we're hearing from people here is that, indeed, that was the case in Tripoli.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Did you know if this is true?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, currently first, and then maybe give me an overview of what you believe is the bigger picture here.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "Well, currently, or the past couple of days?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "It's tough to say, honestly, because you hear a lot of numbers.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "I mean how many people do you think are getting killed here, Adam?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "I truly believe they do, Piers.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Do they have the persistence, do you think, to go through with this?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "LITZER: Well, you should be thinking, first of all, about the young people who are going to die.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "If you're an American watching this, what should you be thinking?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I don't think America should intervene by itself, but it wouldn't be out of the question to see an international coalition get together and do something to try to stop the bloodshed.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "But if you're at the White House and you're making the call here, if this all kicks off in the way some fear it may and we're seeing widespread attacks on the people of Libya, should America intervene?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "I think it's a fascinating dilemma for all European governments right now.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "What are the Europeans going to do?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "There's enormous ramifications for the people of Europe, southern Europe, Italy, especially, but all of those countries are going to watch this.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Big calls for these politicians right now, isn't it?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know, if I knew, boy, I'd be in that next spot.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Where will it end?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Oh, it's huge.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "That's a major escalation, isn't it?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "We should.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Shouldn't we be encouraging and supporting what we're witnessing here?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Yes, we're starting to get reports out of the city of Christchurch, which is in the south islands of New Zealand.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "How bad has this earthquake been?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, what I'm hearing is that Gadhafi is using the air force, using helicopters, bombing Tripoli.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What are you hearing from your sources in Libya?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, good evening, Mr. Morgan.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "How far will he go?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, I believe we've heard his son Saif say that we're going to go down to the last bullet.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "I mean how bad would it get?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Just like every other politician.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What kind of man is he in private when you meet him?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Gentlemen, thank you all very much for your time.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Can I please -- can I come in?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, he allegedly had terminal prostate cancer.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What is your view of that decision?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "UDSON: I think now there's a very excellent opportunity for the full truth to come out.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Do you think you'll ever get any kind of peace or justice?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, justice has been denied to all of us.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Victoria, is there anything he could do now?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, we don't know for sure.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What -- Paul, I was going to ask you, what do you believe prompted the attack on that flight?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, it was the terms of the -- the settlement had been offered to the families as a no-fault settlement.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Why did you do that?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, I think the bottom line is that this regime is doomed.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "With all of your experience, where do you see this going?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I think a first step, it's absolutely crucial that President Obama now come out and state very clearly that the United States is on the side of the Libyan people in this fight, to rally the international community, at least the civilized world to that -- to that call for action.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "What can the west do collectively to try to get involved here?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I wouldn't take it for granted that the regime is going to crumble.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "And if he does go, where would he end up?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I would say that there was clearly, for a long time, several decades, Gadhafi was, in fact, something of America's public enemy number one in the Middle East.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "How would you position Gadhafi?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "In the long term, Piers, it's good news for the economy, in the sense it will be a balanced and more stable economy.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Where do you see this developing?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, I'd agree with it in the short term.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Tom Kloza, would you agree with that assessment?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "It could.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "If that was to happen, that could have a very negative impact on the American economy, couldn't it?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I think the fact that the country shut down the Internet and telecom within the country shows that it was very important.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "How important has the Internet and social networking been in Libya, compared to the other uprisings we've seen?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "It's not necessarily just because the Internet exists?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I think the key is not the fact that this jasmine -- China's Jasmine Revolution failed.", "docId": "110221pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "What are you hearing about China, and whether we can see similar uprisings there, fueled by the Internet and social networking?", "qSentId": 536}]